welcome to FWB Insurance business
kickoff
2024 go go
[Applause]
[Music]
go
I can feel your power for us to kick off
this amazing Dragon Year
2024 ladies and
gentlemen our FWD Insurance business
kickoff is now officially
lost success what is it that makes each
of you different as FWD we've gone
through the transition we've gone
through you know the new product
launches the rebranding so a lot of work
has happened we're now ready to fly the
message is that we are growing
[Music]
fast my aspiration is to when we
accelerate I want to be the fastest
growing insurer in Malaysia I want to be
the fastest growing in 2024 are you with
me FWD onwards up
word
[Music]
together ladies and gentlemen sh
High
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for coming in the spirit this
evening of Shanghai night have a Fant
fantastic year uh may it be filled with
prosperity good success for everyone and
each and
[Music]
everyone
FWD
[Applause]